hoonur.com 2011-10-16

# Hoonur | Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website and for taking an interest in our products. We would like to safeguard the information you provide to us about yourself and inform you of options available to you when using our website and related services. Please read the following policy to understand how personal information you provide us will be used. As this policy may be modified from time to time, please check back periodically.

This is the Privacy Policy governing your usage of Hoonur.com and informs you about the collection, use, transfer and processing of your information by the site.

By using this Site, you agree with our Privacy Policy as listed below.

1\. Information policy

_Registration Information:_

When you sign up with Hoonur, you become a registered user of the site.

You will be asked to provide details such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business and services.

_Publishing Information:_

If you submit any information to Hoonur, we will publish it on the site with your prior consent.

_Statistical Information:_

As a policy, we also collect aggregate statistical information about your usage such as IP addresses, browser software, operating systems, pages viewed, number of sessions etc.

This helps us to understand your usage patterns so we can enhance your experience at Hoonur.

2\. How does Hoonur use my information?

Some of the content you share and the actions you take will show up on your friends’ home pages and other pages they visit.

Generally, Hoonur uses the personal data which you have provided to us for the purposes of fulfilling your application for any of our products, credit checks in the case of applications, and for understanding how we can improve our services to you. Where appropriate, we may also use the information for internal research on our user’s demographics, interests and behavior. and may also use your collected information to improve its marketing and promotional efforts, analyze user patterns and improve on the product and services it offers.

Your information allows us to customize the site lay out and content and make it more convenient for you.

We may also use your information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us.

Some of the content you share and the actions you take will show up on your friends’ and/or followers home pages and other pages they visit.

Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings or it was copied or stored by other users.

You understand that information might be re-shared or copied by other users. Certain types of communications that you send to other users cannot be removed, such as messages.

When you post information on another user’s profile or comment on another user’s post, that information will be subject to the other user’s privacy settings.

If you use an external source to publish information on Hoonur.com (such as a mobile application or a Connect site), you should check the privacy setting for that post, as it is set by that external source.

You will not solicit login information or access an account belonging to someone else. You will not post content that: is hateful, threatening, or pornographic; incites violence; or contains nudity or graphic or gratuitous violence.

You consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in India.

We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may provide your Collected Information to our affiliates and service providers under contract (such as customer care) to support the operation of the Site and our services. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users.

Where appropriate, we may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message. Your Collected Information may be transferred, stored, used and processed outside your home jurisdiction. In case of a merger with or transfer of business to another business entity, we will transfer your Collected Information to the entity which acquires the business (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your Collected Information).

Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The data protection practices of those web sites linked to Hoonur are not covered by this policy statement. You are advised to check the data protection policies of these third party websites yourself before using those sites.

Special Provisions Applicable to Share Links:

If any person/entity includes Hoonur’s Share Link button on its website, the following additional terms shall be applicable to such person/entity: 

  * You shall be permitted to use Hoonur’s Share Link button so that users can post links or content from your website on Hoonur.
  * You give us permission to use and allow others to use such links and content on Hoonur and undertake full responsibility of the content posted. 

_Registration Information:_

We may use your Registration Information and/or the Collected Information to provide services that you request and for the purpose of carrying out promotional and business activities by the Balaji or any of its Group companies and any other marketing agent/s and/or contractors with whom the Company enters, or has entered into any arrangement, in connection with providing of services/products, including without limitation, promotion of various business products. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.

_Publishing Information:_

All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose on Hoonur becomes public information therefore we request you to be careful before you decide to include personal information in the publishing information section.

_Statistical Information:_

We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance our Site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We may provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.

3\. Co-Branded Relationships

We have established relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our Site, or through offering "co-branded" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same uniform resource locator, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. In some cases you may be required to submit information for purposes of registering or applying for products or services provided by such third parties or co-branded partners. The privacy policy of such other parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or co-branded sites. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding to any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.

4\. Cookies

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users.

A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. It can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, Publishing Information or Payment Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patters and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable.

5\. Minors

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

6\. Security Measures

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.
